onethor.com 2014-12-19

# ONE THOR - The Future Now!

To demonstrate ONE THOR’s commitment in protecting your personal data and inform you about how we use it, we have created our Privacy Policy that applies only to the operations and activities in which you are involved, as well as data gathered in our website “www.onethor.com”, either as “visitor”, “partner customer” or “partner company”.

## Description

When you normally access and use our website, we gather various information about you. This Privacy Policy describes which data we collect and how we use them. When accepting our Privacy Policy you expressly agree with the use and disclosure by us of your personal data as provided herein. Our Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Commercial Partnership Agreement.

## Data Gathering

When you are browsing through the website “www.onethor.com” we do not collect any data from you, however once you wish to use the features and tools available you will be required to register and provide some data. These data may include your full name, identification documents, address, ZIP code, phone number, email, birth date, gender, etc. In case you are not willing to provide such personal data, none of our services and products will be available for you.  
Your purchases, sales, records and the content of the communications between you and other users will be automatically recorded for analysis in order to better understand, protect and serve you and our partner network. Including information about your computer’s browser and IP address.

## Cookies

We do not collect information from visitor’s cookies, neither from partners registered in our system.

## Data Gathering By Third Parties

This Privacy Policy is valid only for the use and disclosure of information collected by the website “www.onethor.com”. In our pages there are some links to websites operated by third parties. Some of those websites are from other intellectual property. When clicking on them, regardless of the intellectual property, please be aware that this Privacy Policy is not applied to them. We advise you to read the privacy policy terms on websites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for their actions of gathering and use of information.

## Use Of Personal Data

All the information we collect from you may be used to improve the operation of our system, statistics analysis, advertising contents, order submissions and confirmations, sending of newsletters and promotional emails (optional), customer service and support, payment management and potential adversities with third party companies, calculation of commissions and awards and to ensure compliance with the commercial partnership agreement and with the terms of the company’s Charter of Ethical Principles. We do not sell or rent your personal data to third parties without your express consent. We can, however, gather and disclose personal demographic data in a manner that does not identifies you individually. The suppliers contracted by ONE THOR to execute services in various sectors may have access to your personal data and they will only use the personal data made available by ONE THOR to execute the agreed functions.  
We may be obliged to disclose personal information to the State or third parties in certain circumstances.  
Private information or communications can be illegally intercepted or accessed by third parties or other users can abuse or misuse your personal data which we have gathered on “www.onethor.com”. Therefore, although we use the best industry practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, nor it may be required from us, that your personal data and communications will be always maintained private.

## Widgets

n our site you find widgets and social media features, such as the “Like” and “Share” buttons from Facebook. These widgets and social media features are hosted by third parties and the user interactions with these features are relative to the privacy policy of the providing companies.

## Safety

We take safety measures to protect all against the misuse and alterations of data in our system. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) is among the best programs available on the market and all your personal data are encrypted. We have the SHIELDED WEBSITE certificate, which performs daily thousands of vulnerability analysis of web applications, servers and network devices.

## Reminder

Our Privacy Policy may be altered. Each time you visit ONE THOR’s website or provide us information, you declare to agree with the practices described on this Privacy Policy.

## Questions and Suggestions

In case of questions or suggestions about this privacy policy or even about the “www.onethor.com” website practices, please contact us through the email privacy@onethor.com.
